<?xml version="1.0"?>
<QuoteList>
   <Quote>
    <QuoteText>I do not feel obliged to believe that the same God who has endowed us with sense, reason, and intellect has intended us to forgo their use.</QuoteText>
    <Author>Galileo Galilei</Author>
  </Quote>
   <Quote>
     <QuoteText>I love deadlines. I like the whooshing sound they make as they fly by.</QuoteText>
     <Author>Douglas Adams</Author>
   </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <QuoteText>Every composer knows the anguish and despair occasioned by forgetting ideas which one had no time to write down.</QuoteText>
    <Author>Hector Berlinoz</Author>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <QuoteText>For disappearing acts, it's hard to beat what happens to the eight hours supposedly left after eight of sleep and eight of work.</QuoteText>
    <Author>Doug Larson</Author>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <QuoteText>But the fact that some geniuses were laughed at does not imply that all who are laughed at are geniuses. They laughed at Columbus, they laughed at Fulton, they laughed at the Wright brothers. But they also laughed at Bozo the Clown.</QuoteText>
    <Author>Carl Sagan</Author>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <QuoteText>Freedom is never more than one generation away from extinction. We didn't pass it to our children in the bloodstream. It must be fought for, protected, and handed on for them to do the same, or one day we will spend our sunset years telling our children and our children's children what it was once like in the United States where men were free.</QuoteText>
    <Author>Ronald Reagan</Author>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <QuoteText>Liberty means responsibility. That is why most men dread it.</QuoteText>
    <Author>George Bernard Shaw</Author>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <QuoteText>I get up every morning determined to both change the world and to have one heck of a good time. Sometimes, this makes planning the day difficult.</QuoteText>
    <Author>E.B. White</Author>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <QuoteText>Wise men talk because they have something to say; fools, because they have to say something.</QuoteText>
    <Author>Plato</Author>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <QuoteText>The significant problems we face cannot be solved at the same level of thinking we were at when we created them.</QuoteText>
    <Author>Albert Einstein</Author>
  </Quote>
  <Quote>
    <QuoteText>Don’t spend your life crying over what was not. That's real sickness, and most of us do; what you should have done, what you could have done. That’s gone, that’s finished, it brought you to where you are now. The question now is; What are you DOING about it??</QuoteText>
    <Author>Dr. Leo Buscaglia</Author>
  </Quote>
  
</QuoteList>


